delicious?
美味しい?
Eat another one.
もう一つ食べて
Were you hungry?
お腹空いてた?
Yeah.
うん
Were you hungry?
お腹空いてた?
It was empty.
空いてた
Yeah.
うん
How's school going these days?
最近さ、学校とかどう?
fun.
楽しい
fun?
楽しい?
Yeah.
うん
The appearance has changed somehow.
なんか登場が変わったね
Yeah.
うん
It's been a while.
もう久しぶりだからさ
Yeah.
うん
Something like that.
なんかね
It started to sound like music.
音楽っぽくなったね
Does it sound like music?
音楽っぽくなった?
delicious.
美味しい
I couldn't take it anymore.
取れなくなっちゃった
This is where I ate.
ここら辺、俺食べたところだな
delicious.
美味しい
yeah?
ん?
I don't know how to eat anymore.
食べ方わかんなくなった
Huh, how do you eat this?
え、これどうやって食べるの?
I couldn't take it anymore.
取れなくなっちゃった
It's blinding.
まぶないよ
Well, how do I take it?
え、どうやって取るの?
looks delicious.
美味しそう
What's the weather like today?
今日天気だね
Yeah.
うん
What are you doing at home these days?
最近家で何してるの?
Watching YouTube or playing games.
YouTube見るか、ゲームしてるって
Are you watching You Tube?
You Tube見てんの?
Yeah, I watch YouTube.
うん、YouTube見てる
What kind of videos are you watching?
どんな動画見てる?
Diet stuff.
ダイエットのやつ
diet?
ダイエット?
There's no need to do that.
する必要ないじゃん
Because I just ate it.
今食べちゃったから
Yeah.
うん
Hey, if I were to go on a diet,
ちょっとじゃあ、ダイエットがあったら、
Shall we go for a little walk?
ちょっと歩きに行こうか
2nd one.
2個目
I love you, Amaya.
好 きなんだ、アマヤの
really like.
大好き
A little bit when you look like an adult.
大人っぽくなったらちょっと
Is it true?
本当ですか?
cute.
可愛い
What's up lately?
最近どうなん?
As for life.
生活の方は
Recently, I've been studying at school and working part-time.
最近は、学校の勉強とアルバイトしてる
There aren't any classes at school right now, right?
学校今授業ないんじゃない?
I'm taking it online.
オンライン受けてる
Ah, that's right.
あ、そうなんだ
I see.
そっか
cute.
可愛い
I thought you'd never meet me again.
もう会ってくれないかと思ったよ
Sorry about that earlier.
ちょっとごめんね、前は
It was scary, right?
怖かったでしょ?
It was scary.
怖かった
A sign that your stomach is healed.
お腹直りの印
Can I eat it?
食べていい?
that.
それ
It's delicious here.
ここうまいね、ここ
Yeah, it's delicious.
うん、おいしい
hey.
ね
Haven't you had a boyfriend lately?
最近はなんか、彼氏とかいない?
not present.
いない
not present?
いない?
not present.
いない
Who is your favorite person?
好きな人とかは?
Apparently not.
ないそう
Why isn't that?
なんでそれないの?
Are you studying hard?
勉強頑張ってる?
Yeah.
うん
Are you working hard?
頑張ってる?
Yeah.
うん
I want to support you, Mei-chan.
応 援したいからさ、めいちゃんのこと
Wow, you must have been hungry.
すごい、お腹空いてたんだね
Can you still go?
まだいけるっしょ?
eat.
食べる
Haven't you eaten anything?
なんも食べてなかった?
Yeah.
うん
I see.
そっか
I'm so happy to see you after a long time.
めっちゃ嬉しい、久々に会えて
You've become so cute, seriously.
可愛くなったな、マジ
Are you watching?
見てる?
look
見
Eru?
える?
Yeah.
うん
Is there anyone?
人 いる?
Are you embarrassed?
恥ずかしい?
Yeah.
うん
Can't resist?
我慢できない?
Yeah.
うん
Look, there's a lot of people there?
見て、人いっぱいいる?
Are you embarrassed?
恥ずかしい?
Well then,
じゃあさ、
I'm taking pictures of the room, so let's just go to this place.
部 屋撮ってるから、これだけのところに行こうか
hey.
ね
I won't do anything that scary today.
今日そんな怖いことしないからね
Was it delicious?
美味しかった?
ice.
アイス
It was delicious.
美味しかったです
I passed two.
2つも通っちゃったね
Yeah.
うん
It's been a while.
久しぶりだね
久しぶりです
How have you been?
元気だった?
fine.
元気
I tried to contact you once, but I couldn't get in touch with you at all.
一回連絡がさ、全く取れなくなっちゃったからさ
Yeah.
うん
If you want to meet other people,
他の、他の人と会おうと思ったら、
I was directed away by the police and couldn't get in touch.
警察の人で誘導されちゃって、 連絡取れなくなっちゃった
Were you induced?
誘導されちゃったの?
Seriously?
マジで?
Eh, was it okay?
えー、大丈夫だった?
it's okay.
大丈夫です
We simply lost contact with each other,
これも連絡単純に取れなくなって、
I've been getting a lot of calls from numbers I don't recognize.
なんか知らない番号からめっちゃ電話かかってきたから
But somehow, amazingly, he gradually started to open up to me.
でもなんか、すごい、 だんだん心を開いてくれるようになって
hey.
ね
Since then, I've met him from time to time.
あれ からね、ちょいちょい会ってくれたもんね
Let's go on a date.
デートしたりね
Eating Yakiniku.
焼肉食べたりね
You were scared last time a while ago, right?
ちょっと前、前回怖かったでしょ?
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
Are you okay.
大丈夫
How is school?
学校はどうなの?
School is tough, but I'm doing well.
学校、大変だけど、ちゃんと行ってる
yes?
そう?
it was good.
良かった
He looks fine.
元気そうなんだよ
Fair enough, what is it, ice cream?
割ともね、 なんだっけ、アイス、
Ice cream shop.
アイスクリーム屋さん
I like it, really.
好きなんだね、ほんとね
really like.
大好き
I'm sorry for just a moment, but...
ちょっとさっきごめんね、なんか、
I was so horny that I let it out, but
すごいムラムラしてて、 出しちゃったけど、
Suddenly.
急に
Can I do something like this today?
今日もさ、ようなことしていい?
No erotic titles?
エッチタイトルもしてない?
What about sex?
エッチは?
I am doing.
してます
Haven't you?
してない?
Let's put it down a little.
ちょっと下出しておく
Take a break for the first time in a while.
久々に休憩してね
You look so grown up.
すごい大人っぽいね
Are you hungry?
お腹すいた?
Wow, you were so childish.
すごい、お前子供っぽいやつだったのにね
Just like that, can you spread the word?
そのままさ、広めいてもらう?
It's interesting.
面白いですよ
Hey, get on your knees and ride the tsunpa.
ちょっとさ、 膝つけてよ、ツンパに乗ってください
Stick your butt out, more.
お尻突き出してくれ、もっと
Put your hands behind your back
手後ろにしてく
Re.
れ
Why don't you open your pussy yourself?
自 分でおもんこ開いてごらん?